吃你的西兰花
Eat your broccoli.
我给客厅置办了一套天鹅绒的组合家具
I found a velvet sectional for the living room.
然后我还放了些植物 你知道的 鹅掌柴
I put some plants behind it, you know, scheffleras.
阿莱塔新开了一家漂亮的植物店
There is a gorgeous new plant store in Arleta.
看来我还是喜欢阿莱塔的 晚上别去那儿
Turns out I like Arleta. Don't go there at night.
特蕾莎需要一架大钢琴
Oh, and Theresa needs a grand piano.
我们这是在骗谁呢
I mean, who are we fooling with this upright?
她太优秀了
She's too good.
这件事我们得拖一段时间了
We're gonna have to hold off on this stuff
好吗
for a while, all right?
为什么
Why?
钱去哪了 文斯 它就这样消失了吗
Where'd the money go, Vince? Did it just disappear?
这几个月难熬罢了
It's been a tough couple of months.
是啊 如果你继续让约翰尼帮你记账的话
Oh, yeah, it's gonna be a tough year
今年会一直难熬的
if you keep letting Johnny do your books.
嘿 这就是生意 不是你要考虑的问题
Hey, that's business. That's not your problem.
是啊
Oh, yes, it is.
你知道谁从来不会赔钱
You know who never loses money,
谁会像老鹰一样
who tracks every cent
盯着屋里的每一分钱
that comes in this house like a hawk?
-你不会喜欢那样的  -我谢谢你
- Not that you'd appreciate it. - I appreciate you.
我需要一个新洗碗机
And I need a new dishwasher.
这里太热了
It's hot in here.
这架钢琴有多大呢
How big of a piano are we talking about?
你说呢
You tell me.
你很擅长把东西塞进狭小的空间里
you're better at fitting things in tight spaces.
好吧 钢琴 但其他东西
Okay, the piano, but the other stuff--
不不不 我完全理解
No, no, no, I totally understand,
-相当理解  -很好
- completely understand. - Good.
有个惊喜
I got a surprise.
-有人在卡车上找到了这个  -天呐
- Guys got this off a truck. - Oh, my God.
焕然一新
Brand-spanking-new.
也许会让你心情好点
Might put you in the mood.
天呐
Oh, oh, my.
你没告诉我你的第二份工作是当模特
You didn't tell me you got a second job modeling.
现在单身女孩拿到避孕药了
这是什么
What the hell is this?
传递一条任性蛇的新闻
不不不 路易 我知道了
No, no, no, no, Louie. I got it.
没问题 我会解决的
No problem. I-I'll fix this.
好吧 不 谢谢你
Okay, no, thank you.
我该找谁要零用现金呢
Uh, who do I go to for petty cash?
我们需要一些
We need some set pieces
意大利文艺复兴时期的作品
that read Italian Renaissance.
别管它了 布里格 我们有更大的麻烦了
Put that on ice, Prigger. We got a bigger problem.
我们和黑帮有生意往来
We're in business with the Mob,
就是那些会打架
with the literal Mob
非法贩卖威士忌酒的黑帮吗
who whack people and bootleg whiskey?
虽然现在不是20世纪20年代 但没错
Well, it's not the 1920s, but, yeah.
你从来没想过告诉我黑手党
You never thought to tell me
会运输我的杂志吗
that the Mafia delivers my magazine?
开卡车的人会派送我们的杂志
Guys in trucks deliver our magazines,
他们受雇于船运公司
and they are employed by shipping companies
他们可能与犯罪集团有联系 也可能没有
who may or may not, but absolutely do,
但绝对有联系
have ties to organized crime.
那我们换一个经销商吧
Well, then Iet's get a different distributor.
很好 那你想知道
Great, you know anybody who wants
谁明天会把所有的卡车都烧了吗
all their trucks set on fire tomorrow?
好吧 他们是天主教徒
Okay, so they're-- they're Catholic enough
一篇关于节育的文章足够可以冒犯到他们
to be offended by an article on birth control,
但他们对那些淫秽的修女不也还是纵容了吗
but yet they're somehow fine with naughty nuns?
乔伊斯 这些人很复杂
These are complicated people, Joyce.
杂七杂八的人聚在一起
They contain multitudes.
别用我崇拜的英雄来安慰我
Don't quote my heroes back to me.
你这么做真让人恼火
It's so irritating when you do that.
不要
Don't--
他们可能只是忽略了我文章中的细微之处
They probably just blew past the nuances in my article.
如果我和他们谈谈呢
What if I talk to 'em
和他们讲讲计划生育的好处
and--and I explain the benefits of family planning?
你是那种在死前
Are you one of those people
一有机会就兴奋起来的人吗
who gets turned on the moment before you die?
谁能准确地回答这个问题呢
How could anybody answer that with any accuracy?
你就这么屈服了吗
You're just giving in?
不 我在努力让《风骚女子》重新上架
No, I'm getting "Minx" back on the shelves.
现在这本杂志可以派送了
This is now a shippable magazine.
解决了一本 还有49万9千本要解决
One down and 499,000 to go.
不客气 拿起杂志
You're welcome. Grab a magazine.
让你花了很长很长的时间
♪ Getting you took a long, long time ♪
你叫什么名字 你还好吗
♪ What's your name? Are you feeling fine? ♪
拉把椅子过来 分点酒给你
♪ Pull up a chair, share my wine ♪
嘿 他们在那儿
Hey, there they are.
闭上眼 进来
♪ Close your eyes, come inside ♪
别担心我们
Don't worry about us.
我们进出的速度会比参议员进妓院还快
We will be in and out quicker than a senator in a whorehouse.
给你 道格·雷内蒂 袋底钱
There you go. Doug Renetti, Bottom Dollar.
道格·雷内蒂 袋底钱 谢谢
Doug Renetti, Bottom Dollar. Thank you.
你应该知道你的杂志已经被地方限制了吧
You do realize your magazine's already broken out
全堆在仓库了
by region-- like, all over the warehouse.
你得到处去推销
You gonna have to go around pulling bundles.
这得花上一周的时间
It's gonna take all week.
好了 斑比 你是开页员
All right, Bambi, you are our page opener,
里奇 订书钉清理员 雪莉 文章提取员
Richie, staple remover, Shelly, article extractor,
还有蒂娜 最后收整好你是我们的订书机
and, Tina, bringing it all home as our re-stapler.
嗯 我觉得我们应该
Um, yeah, you know, I think we should--
嗯 其实我很擅长做起钉器的工作
Yeah, um, I'm actually a natural staple remover.
明天是摄影日
- Oh. - It's a shoot day tomorrow.
这双手不能靠近尖锐的东西
These shouldn't be near anything sharp.
明白了
Gotcha.
我喜欢这个
Ooh, I like that.
我今天不想死
I'm-- I'm not trying to die today.
明天的插页照片
Big centerfold shoot tomorrow.
-我们扮演大卫  -尼文
- We're doing "David." - Oh, Niven?
-不 是米开朗基罗  -那是我的乔伊斯
- Uh, no, Michelangelo. - Oh, that's my Joyce-y.
这就是我想说的
This is what I'm talking about right here--
一流团队设立标准
the A-team setting the standard.
-我很喜欢看到这一幕  -这要花多久
- I love to see it. - How long is this gonna take?
我办公室有很多事要做
I have so much to do at the office.
我们完事就走 怎么样
We'll Ieave when we're done. How's that?
-我建议找临时工  -是 但他们不在乎
- I suggested day laborers. - Yeah, but they don't care.
他们是雇佣兵 他们会像一群狼一样
They're mercenaries, just ripping apart our magazine
把我们的杂志撕成碎片的
like a pack of wolves.
不 我雇的都是优秀的人
No, I hire good people who give a shit.
我去和他们谈谈
I'll go talk to 'em.
我去买咖啡
And I will get coffee.
虽然我对脚不感兴趣
Mm, now, I don't have a thing for feet,
但看看那些小脚趾
but check out those little piggies.
我想把它们拿到市场上去卖
I'd like to take them to market.
就像你们一样 先生们
As you were, gentlemen.
我也不是每天都能看到
It's nothing I don't see every single day.
事实上 我其实是这张照片的顾问
In fact, I actually consulted on this photo shoot,
所以我们淘气的老师
which is why our naughty teacher
才把书正面朝上
is holding the book right side up.
你们能不能给我指一下咖啡的方向
I wonder if you could point me in the direction of the coffee.
在柜子里 但罐子破了
It's in the cabinet, but the pot's cracked.
不好意思 在上了18个小时的班后
Excuse me, after an 18-hour shift,
你也会水肿的
you might get a case of the dropsies, too.
18个小时 这也太漫长了
18 hours? That is a long day.
胶带在橱柜里
Tape is in the cabinet.
-谢谢  -很好
- Oh, merci. - Right on.
你的手怎么了
What happened to your hand?
佛雷特比卡罗 一比零
Forklift, one. Carlos, zero.
知道了
Noted.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
嗯
Oh, yeah.
仓库里的通风系统简直就是狗屎
Ventilation in the warehouse is dog shit.
还有卡车冒出的烟雾
Fumes from the trucks.
先生们 我不是想过分赞扬现任政府
Well, gentlemen, not to give our current administration
但他们两年前
too much credit, but they did pass
确实通过了
federal workplace safety regulations
联邦工作场所安全条例
two years ago.
-你们听说过职业安全和健康署吧  -职业安全和健康署
Surely you've heard of OSHA? - OSHA?
是啊 你不必在这种糟糕的条件下工作
Yeah, you don't have to labor in these awful conditions.
你们像所有的工作者一样是有权利的
You, like all workers, have rights.
-还要几天 蒂娜  -这不关我的事 菲尔
- How many more days, Tina? - Not my call, Phil.
工作完成后就结束吧
When the job's done, it'll be done.
但修复《风骚女子》不是我们的工作
But fixing "Minx" is not our job.
我自己有四款盈利颇丰的杂志
I have four profitable titles of my own.
我昨天一整天都像个农夫一样
I spent all day yesterday hauling magazine bales
拖着杂志包
like a goddamn farmer.
货车9点出发
Van leaves at 9: 00.
这可不像艾迪
Oh, that doesn't look like Eddie.
-这不是艾迪  -谁是艾迪
- It's not Eddie. - Who is Eddie?
我们预定拍摄的蛇 但这不是艾迪
The snake we book for shoots, but that's not Eddie.
好吧 听着 我们被父权制社会社会化了
All right, okay, look, we have been socialized
认为自己是需要被拯救的受害者
by the patriarchy to think of ourselves
但我们是
as victims who need to be rescued,
自由的女性
but we're liberated women.
我们可以拯救自己
We can clearly just rescue ourselve--
好吧 好吧 好吧
All right, okay, all right. Okay, all right.
嘿 伙计 你迷路了吗
Aw, hi, friend. Are you lost?
没关系的
It's okay.
我们去给你找个新家
We're gonna find you a new home.
停车场怎么样
What about the parking lot?
那里后面的小沟里 我看到有一群老鼠
In a little ditch back there, I saw a bunch of mice.
看起来很有意思 是吧小可爱
Seems like a fun time. Yes, cutie.
好了 我们得贴个标语
Bleh! Okay, we have got to put up a sign,
确保人们不要让门开着
make sure people do not leave the door open.
你觉得那东西是自己溜进来的吗
You think that thing slithered in on a its own?
这是个威胁
That was a threat. - Oh.
消息收到了 路易 蛇也收到了
Message received, Louie, and snake received.
不不不不不 我不是在指责你
No, no, no, no, no, I'm not accusing you.
我只是在传递一条任性的蛇的消息
I'm-- I'm simply relaying news of a wayward snake.
重点是我绝对会处理好这件事的
The point is, is I will handle this 100%.
你善良又通情达理
You are as reasonable as you are kind.
谢谢 拜拜
T-thank you. Bye.
布里格
Prigger!
你为什么总认为是我的错
Why do you always assume that it's my fault?
那还有哪个别的傻逼
Oh, was it some other jackass in a pussy bow
会教育他们工人的权利
riling up the warehouse guys,
导致惹毛了仓库的人
educating them about workers' rights?
那个环境非常不安全
It's a wildly unsafe environment.
就算是黑帮也不希望他们的员工
Surely even the Mob doesn't want their employees
-死在工作中吧  -他们是黑帮
dying on the job. - They're the Mob.
要没有这一点就不是他们了
They're famous for being okay with that.
那我是坏人喽
And I'm the bad guy here.
听着 孩子
Listen to me, kid.
我要从没有《风骚女子》到不能出任何杂志了
I went from having no "Minx" to no magazines at all.
因为你 他们不会派送我们的东西了
They won't deliver anything of mine because of you.
我跟这些人做了15年生意
15 years I'm in business
都没有问题
with these people, no problem.
你来了六个星期
You're here six weeks,
我都不知道自己还有没有生意了
and I don't know if I have a business anymore.
要是这么脆弱
Well, if it's that fragile, I might argue
我可能会说你根本就没有生意
that you don't have a business at all, really.
别和我犟
Don't you take the high road on me.
所以你打入工人内部了吗 你是冠军吗
So you're into workers now? You're their champion?
-是吗  -当然
Is that it? - Sure.
站起来 看看窗外
Stand up. Look out the window.
请站起来
I mean it. Stand up, please.
看窗外
Look out the window.
你看到那些人了吗
You see all these people? - Mm-hmm.
因为你他们都要朝不保夕了
Well, their asses are on the line because of you.
好吧 好吧 很显然有一个
All right, okay, surely there is
-简单的解决办法  -是
a simple solution here. - Yeah, there is.
你的愿望要实现了 你去和黑帮谈谈
You're gonna get your wish. You're gonna talk to the Mob.
真不敢相信我错过了这个
I cannot believe I'm missing this,
但我确定你需要的一切都在这里
but I'm sure that everything you need is right in here.
雪莉知道我想要什么 所以
Oh, and Shelly knows what I want, so...
我不知道他应该看向哪里
I'm not sure where exactly he's supposed to be looking.
远离相机
Away from camera.
这就是风骚女子令人意想不到的转折点
That's the "Minx" twist. Oh.
大卫是理想化的男性美
"The David" is idealized male beauty.
这是一个招致物化的雕塑
It's a sculpture that invites objectification,
但就像我们拒绝男人看女人一样
but just as we reject men looking at women,
我们也拒绝男人看女人看男人
we also reject men looking at women looking at men.
但他已经把目光移开了
But he's already looking away.
是的 所以我们让他
Yes, that's why we having him looking away
看向另一个方向
but in the opposite direction.
它颠覆了期望
It subverts expectation.
好吧 戴恩 跳上去
- Oh. - Okay. Uh, Dane, hop up there.
-我应该看别处吗  -你会习惯的
- Am I supposed to look away? - You'll get used to it.
是的 大概是这样的 但我得走了
Yeah, that's the rough idea, I guess, but I have to go.
我知道你会搞定的
So, um, I know you'll make it sing.
乔伊斯
Joyce
他就把东西放那吗
Is he just gonna leave that there?
我的天哪
Lord in Heaven.
这能撑多久
How long is this drive?
这些巧克力屌在阳光下放不了多久的
Those chocolate dicks are not gonna hold up in the sun.
-你觉得它们会融化吗  -让开
- Think they're gonna melt? - Move over.
你根本没有准备东西的天分
You have no flair for presentation.
好吧 谢谢
All right. Thank you.
今天会是不错的一天
Today's gonna go good.
我要去参加小维托的舞会
I'm gonna go to this little shindig for Little Vito,
和那个大块头打个视频电话
get some face time with the big man,
然后 我们就能重新工作了
and, boom, we'll be back in business.
要是早知道公司的命运会押在一件T恤上
If I knew the fate of our company came down to a T-shirt,
我就选择百分百纯棉的了
I would've sprung for a 100% cotton.
你确定你能处理好这些吗
You sure you're cool to hold down the fort?
你能踩着华尔兹舞步去黑帮老大家吗
You cool with waltzing into a Mob boss' house?
拜托 这些是洛杉矶的黑帮
Oh, come on, these are L.A. gangsters.
离西西里越远
The danger peters out
就越不危险
the further you get from Sicily.
怎么回事 你是在担心我吗
What is going on? Are you worried about me?
我只是担心用这个问题
I'm just not sure bringing the problem
来解决这个解决问题的问题不太好
to solve the problem solves the problem.
好吧 除非你有什么门路
All right, well, unless you got any connections
能和一个敌对的犯罪家族扯上关系
to a rival crime family...
否则这就是我们唯一的办法了
I think this is our only move.
这件怎么样
what do you think?
这条宽松裤很配水泥鞋
Cement shoes are gonna go great with those slacks.
说吧 让我听听 练习一下
All right, go ahead. Let me hear it. Practice.
带点激情
With pep.
很抱歉我在你的仓库里
I'm sorry I sowed seeds
播下了怨恨的种子
of resentment at your warehouse.
乔伊斯
Joyce...
你是来亲吻戒指 表达尊重的好吗
you are there to kiss the ring, okay?
得了吧 他又不是教皇
Oh, please. He's not the Pope.
况且那家伙也不是很能干
Not that that guy is any great shakes either, by the way,
-他对于同性恋的政策  -不 乔伊斯
- His policy on homo-- - No, Joyce.
你是去向小维托道歉
You're there to apologize and to congratulate Little Vito
并祝贺他的成就 结婚或者出狱
on getting made, married, or out of jail.
在任何情况下 你都不能说教 发狂
Under no circumstances do you preach, rabble-rouse,
或者对那些有权势的人说真话 别乔伊斯
or speak truth to power-- no Joyce-ing.
我倒不知道我现在还是个动词了
Oh- ho, I didn't realize I was a verb now.
也有可能
And maybe, you know,
我反对你的话
just to play devil's advocate,
我们来这里不是因为乔伊斯行为很有效吗
aren't we here because Joyce-ing is effective?
我刺激了那些工人 不是吗
I-I activated those workers, didn't I?
抱歉 你想表达什么
I'm so sorry. What is your argument here?
我想说也许我就是
That maybe I'm the perfect person
改变一些人关于生育权想法的
to change a few hearts and minds
-完美人选  -知道吗
- about reproductive rights. - Okay, you know what?
我认为他们已经在避孕药问题上
I think they made their position on the pill
表达清楚了他们的立场
crystal clear, Prigger.
要不我们就接受他们的话
Why don't we take them at their word
别再惹他们生气了行吗
and stop pissing 'em off?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我很好 没事
Yeah, I'm grea-- yes.
-好了 再练习一下  -天哪
All right, practice, go again. - Oh, my God!
维托 别跑太远
Vito, Vito, don't go too far!
不许在拉森家院子里撒尿
And no peeing in the Larsons'yard!
是来找文斯的吧
Must be here for Vince.
跟我来吧 把门关上
Follow me. Get the door.
小维托
Little Vito?
我以为是戏称
I thought it was ironic,
就像瘦乔伊或帅汤姆之类的
like Thin Joey or Handsome Tom, okay?
BGM:《Somewhere beyond the Sea》
在海洋的
♪ Somewhere ♪
彼岸之外
♪ Beyond the sea ♪
她期盼着我归来
♪ She's there watching for me ♪
如果我能
♪ If I could fly ♪
-如鸟儿一样飞翔  -球出界了
♪ Like birds on high ♪ - The ball is out!
我会直接飞向
♪ Then straight to her arms ♪
她的怀抱
♪ I'd go sailing ♪
文斯 有工作伙伴
Hey, Vince, some work friends are here
在你儿子的生日这天来找你了
at your son's birthday.
我是底袋钱的道格·雷内蒂 这位是
Doug Renetti, Bottom Dollar, and this is--
来吧 女孩们都在厨房里
Come on, honey. Girls are in the kitchen.
不了 我在这挺好的
Oh, no, I'm fine here.
还是去厨房吧
I'd say just go in the kitchen.
不 我们要在这里聊呢
No, it's-- this is where all the action is.
相信我 你会觉得无聊的
Believe me, you'll be bored out of your mind, sweetheart.
-去吧  -计划有变
- Go. - Plans change.
去交点朋友吧 有机会我会把你叫回来的
Go make friends. I'll pull you in if I can.
走吧 厨房里快忙不过来了
Come on, hon. We need help in the kitchen.
打个赌吗
Help me settle a bet, will you?
我赌每个留胡子的人都是弱鸡
I say every man with a beard has a weak chin.
你真幽默
You got me.
要脱鞋哦 我们刚擦好地板
Oh, shoes off, hon. We just polished the floors.
姑娘们 这是乔伊斯
- Oh. - Girls, this is Joyce.
她和一个大帅哥一起来的
She came in with a very handsome fella.
不不不
- Oh! - No, no, God, no.
-他不是我男朋友  -一个不是她男朋友的人
- He's not my boyfriend. - Who is not her boyfriend.
哇 好像有很多
Wow, seems like there is a lot
不被认可的劳动啊
of unacknowledged labor going on in here.
男人们会来帮忙吗
Do the men ever lift a finger to help--
你来搅拌 我得给蛋糕撒糖霜
Yeah, stir the gravy. I got to frost the cake.
我家只有一辆车 是跑车
So we only had the one car, the GTO,
只有弗雷迪能开
and Freddy had to be the one to drive it.
而且弗雷迪讨厌左转
By the way, Freddy hates left turns.
我们到达目的地前
We'll make smaller and smaller circles
会不停绕圈
till we just get somewhere.
我们可不想弄脏你漂亮的衣服
We don't want to ruin your nice outfit.
这是什么 30美元的西装 威尔希尔的公牛队
What was this, $30? Bullocks on Wilshire.
其实 好的吧
Actually, yes.
于是我等到弗雷迪出城
So I wait till Freddy's out of town,
就去买了一个婴儿汽车座椅 粉红色的
and I go and buy one of those baby car seats, a pink one,
我把它放在跑车里了
and I put it in the GTO.
弗雷迪回来后 它已经变成女士车了
Freddy comes home. Now it's a woman's car.
然后他去给自己买了一辆大众开迪
He goes out and gets himself a Caddy.
-跑车就是我的了  -这招不错
I got the GTO. That's very clever.
但这有点强调性别规范了
But, uh, it reinforces gender norms--
-你能帮我抱一下施特菲吗  -当然
- Will you hold Steffi a sec? - Sure.
天啊 不过我觉得她不太喜欢我
Oh, God, I don't think she likes me, though.
别忘了肉汁
Don't forget the gravy.
要快点吗
Quickly?
你们知道吗 有一个新政策
You know, there is a new movement
叫家庭主
called Wages for House--
喜欢吗
You like?
太好吃了
- That is incredible. - Mm.
问题不在于角度 而是概念
The problem isn't the angle. It's the concept.
那要不我们试试别的
Then why don't we try something else?
毕竟我们已经不整“大卫”那套了
I mean, we're already not doing the "David."
-嗯  -当然
- Mm. - Sure.
看看这家伙的巨手 还有可爱的小丁丁
Look at this guy's giant hands and cute little fella.
你的阴茎比“大卫”人得多
You have a much bigger penis than the "David."
大很多
Much.
在文艺复兴时期的佛罗伦萨
Standards of masculinity were different
男子气概的标准与现在不同
in Renaissance Florence.
大阴茎当时是与
Large penises were associated
愚蠢 丑陋和欲望相关
with foolishness, ugliness, and lust.
《意大利文艺复兴的艺术》
好吧
Oh, okay.
乔伊斯告诉了我们她想要什么样的
Listen, Joyce told us her vision,
我们需要去完成
and we need to execute that.
但我们有搭上一点边吗
But are we even in the neighborhood of arousal here?
如果我们做出亮瞎眼的东西
If we give Joyce something that sparkles,
她会赋予连我们都没发现的意义
I mean, she'll find meaning we didn't even know was there.
她很擅长这个
She is very good at that.
-没错  -是脸的问题
- Mm-hmm. - It's the face thing.
我希望能看到他的脸
I want to see his face.
脸是她唯一要求清楚的事
It's the one thing she was clear about-- the face.
你不能换个镜头什么的吗
Can't you just use a different lens or something?
摄影可不是这样的
Babe, that's not how photography works.
让他上去 我要换个镜头
Get him up there. I'm gonna change the lens.
它有循环功能
And it does a sani cycle.
洗杯子时不会留下斑点
Washes glasses without leaving spots.
路易都不知道
Louie doesn't know it yet,
但他给我买了一个
but he's getting me one of these.
这设计非常巧妙啊
The design is very elegant,
但你知道吗
but it just-- you know what?
像这样的电器只会让女人
Appliances like this just give women
误认为自己会有更多时间
the illusion of more time.
我想要一个 但弗雷迪太小气了
I want one, but Freddy is so cheap.
你一直在形容的
That's consistent with the Freddy
-弗雷迪就是这样  -亲爱的
- you've been describing. - Oh, hon.
施特菲把果汁弄洒了 你能帮我弄一下吗
Steff Just spilled her juice. Will you get that for me?
好
Yes.
你把果汁洒了吗
Did you spill your juice?
弗雷迪 你看到弗朗西的新洗碗机了吗
Freddy, did you see Francie's new dishwasher?
它会浸湿和擦洗
It soaks and scrubs.
看起来很贵
Looks expensive.
哦 我不是在暗示你 我知道我们买不起
Oh, I wasn't suggesting. I know we can't afford it.
但也许几年后
But maybe in a few years
弗朗西丝卡或布伦达买新机器时
when Francesca or Brenda upgrade,
我们可以买他们的旧的
we can get their old one.
路易要给你买一个吗
Louie's getting you one of these?
已经商量好了
It's been discussed.
这周末买一个
Pick one up this weekend.
你说了算
You're the boss.
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
她完全掌控了他
She just totally manipulated him.
该吃生日蛋糕了
Time for birthday cake.
她很好
She's good.
华盛顿            24
公牛队              31
决赛
输的多惨啊 对吧
What a tough loss, right?
但我想我们都知道这种
But I think we all know how it feels
从你身下拔出东西的感觉
to have something pulled out from under you--
-赛后再聊  -好吧
- Postgame, postgame. - Yeah.
看完比赛再说
Let's just finish the postgame.
比利 今天的比赛很艰难
Tough one out there today, Billy.
那些支持者围着我转
Those backers were all over me
就像浣熊身上的虱子
like a tick on a coonhound.
只有一件事要做 摆脱损失
Only one thing left to do-- shake off the loss,
看看公牛队
hit the town, see what kind of tail
有多惨
Buffalo has to offer.
天呐 这是你应得的 比利
- Oh, Jes-- You earned it, Billy.
他们让人不再喜欢他了 对吧
They don't make 'em like him anymore, right?
-不  -一个犯了错误的人
- No, they don't-- a guy who makes mistakes
但不知怎的 为了赢球 他回来了 更加强大
but somehow comes back even stronger for the win--
这是联盟中唯一一个
It's the only position in the league
他们甚至还允许白人打球
where they still allow white guys to even play.
这是最重要的
It's the most important one.
他们需要一个善于谋划的人
They need someone who strategizes good.
他们不让穆利根人加入球队是为了他们太笨
They don't let the mulignans on the team for their brains.
你知道当我年轻的时候 有洋基队吧
You know, when I was young, we had the Yankees, right?
然后他们有了黑人联盟 还蛮好
And then they had a Negro league, and it was fine.
整的还不错
It just worked fine.
杰基·罗宾逊在你意识到之前就想到了
Jackie Robinson comes along, before you know it,
我得雇这些人
I got to hire these people.
是啊 那就是花钱如流水的时候了
Yeah, that's when the money starts walking out the door.
这就是为什么他妈的总是没现金了
That's why there's fucking cash missing all the time.
手脚都不干净
Sticky fingers, every single one of them.
你知道他们怎么说西西里人吗
Well, you know what they say about the Sicilians--
他们不是好黑帮 他们是暴徒
they're no-good gangsters, and they're thugs,
每一个人都是
every single one of them.
你说什么
What'd you just say?
我以为你们会笑的
- I thought you guys were gonna laugh.
我在开玩笑 我自己也是意大利人
I was making a joke. I'm an Italian myself.
哦是吗
Oh, really?
你肯定是纳布里登人对吧
You got to be a Nablidon of course, right?
-我不会说那种语言  -你才不是意大利人
- I don't speak the language. - Oh, you're not Italian.
我不是故意不尊重你
I didn't mean any disrespect.
我最尊重你了
I have nothing but respect for you.
你知道在我的公司 底袋钱
You know, a-at my company, Bottom Dollar,
所有人都为我工作
I got everybody under the sun working for me.
我的首席副手是黑人 一个女人 黑人女人
My top lieutenant's Black-- a woman, Black woman.
她挺好的
- Oh. - She's good, man.
她很好
She's good.
我丢钱的时候 是她
When I had money missing, it was her
知道是谁拿走的
who figured out who took it.
谁偷的 她哥哥吗
Who stole it, her brother?
幽默 不是的 我想说的是
Funny, no, no. All I'm saying is,
如果有人投钱了
if somebody's skimming off the top,
很可能你刚雇佣的 不是一个低层次的人
the chances are it's not a low-level guy you just hired.
可能是最了解你生意的人
It's somebody who knows your business the best.
这是个核心圈
It's the inner circle-
那些让你放松警惕的人
the people you let your guard down around,
那些你以为是你朋友的人
the ones you consider your friends.
要我说 这只是常识
And if you ask me, that's just common se--
增加40%的预算 升级相机
40% budget increase, camera upgrades,
60磅的油彩存货 这是什么
60-pound glossy stock-- what is this?
需求清单 道格已经失去理智了
List of demands. You know Doug has lost it.
我们想要一个公平的工作环境
We want a fair workplace.
风骚女子有的我们也要
We want what "Minx" gets.
-你没工作可干吗  -我们没法干
- Shouldn't you be working? - We can't.
《风骚女子》拍摄时间超了两个小时
"Minx" is two hours over their studio time.
一点都不意外
Big surprise.
维托里奥 该开始了
Vittorio! It's time!
《巧克力辣妹》
维托里奥
Vittorio!
你终于来了 怎么样了
Finally. So?
挺复杂的一次谈判
So it's a complex negotiation.
你都没提到杂志的事 是不是
You haven't even brought up the magazine yet, have you?
-没有  -你怎么流了那么多汗
- Nope. - Why are you so sweaty?
-你的胡子都湿了  -完蛋了
Your beard is really sweaty. - Oh, shit.
-祝你生日快乐  -你的胡子在滴水
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪ - It's dripping.
祝你生日快乐
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday-- ♪
文斯想和你单独谈谈
Vince needs to speak with you one-on-one.
我想先吃块蛋糕呢
I thought I--I was gonna have some cake first.
我强烈反对 快走
I strongly advise against it. Come on.
祝你
♪ To you ♪
每天快乐
♪ And many more ♪
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
一连七个
Seven in a row.
你是怎么做到的 你真的是大卫吗
How are you doing that? Are you actually David?
不是 我是在农场长大的
No, I just grew up on a farm.
好了 该开始工作了
Okay, we have to get back to work.
我重调了所有灯光设置
I changed the whole lighting setup.
就假装我们从来没做过这些
Let's just pretend like we've never done any of this before.
我不是你妈妈 戴恩
I'm not your mother, Dane.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
站上来
Up here.
-抽筋了  -你没事吧
- Oh, cramp. - You okay?
没事 等我一会儿
Ooh, yeah, yeah. Just give me a sec.
好的
- Okay. - Ooh.
-你从哪儿学来的  -茱莉亚音乐学院
- Where'd you learn this? - Juilliard...
体操课上学的 兄弟
calisthenics class, man.
在那里待了一个学期 竞争太激烈了
I went there for a semester-- too competitive.
-好了 我可以了  -不 不
- All right, I'm good. - No, no, no.
继续做你的动作 非常棒
Keep doing what you're doing. It's great.
太好了 保持 伸直
Excellent. Hold that for me, extend.
漂亮 就这样
Gorgeous, stay there. Stay there.
好了 再来个
Okay, give me--
进来 走吧
Come on in. Let's go.
菲尔 我们还在拍摄呢
Hey, Phil, we're still shooting here.
-现在不是了  -菲尔 怎么回事
- Not anymore. - Phil, what's going on?
我们要拍摄了 就是这么回事
We're about to shoot. That's what we're doing.
-这是什么情况  -不知道啊
- What's happening? - I don't know.
不是的 菲儿 我们正在用工作室呢
No, no, Phil, we have the studio.
你已经在这里好几个小时了 该结束了
You've been here for hours. Show's over.
你们在这里待的时间够长了
You guys have been here long enough.
-我正在拍摄呢  -不 不
- I'm in the middle of a shoot. - No, no, no, no.
别这样 别碰我们的书
- Don't! These are-- - Don't touch our books.
女士们 麻烦把衣服穿上好吗
Ladies, no, please. If you could just cover up.
-我们都等了多久了  -嘿
- Been waiting for-- - Hey!
停下 别争了
Stop it! Knock it off!
我知道你不尊重我 但你必须离开
I know that you don't respect me, but you have to go--
这是图书馆借的书
That is a library book.
这是我们的书 太过分了
This is our book! Absolutely--
都他妈给我住手
I said knock it the fuck off!
《风骚女子》 你们拍摄时间太长了
"Minx," you went way over your studio time.
-你们是15份杂志中的一份  -没错 好好给他们说一下
You are one magazine out of 15. - Yeah, you tell 'em.
闭嘴 傻蛋 你也不能一言不合就把人家
Shut up, dumbass. You can't bum-rush a photo shoot
-赶出拍摄棚  -这都是我们的设备
because you're unhappy. - It's all our equipment.
那我们就建立一个确保公平使用场地的制度
So we'll set up a system that ensures equal access.
-我给道格说一下  -道格失去理智了
I'll talk to Doug. - Doug is out of his mind.
如果是这样 那他比你们这些人
Well, if he is, he's earned the right to be
更有资格失去理智
more than anyone else here.
我来提醒一下各位
And I'll remind you that he has taken a chance
他在为这里的每一个人冒险
on every single one of us in this room.
所以 如果有人不喜欢公司的现状
So, if you don't like what's happening at this company,
可以走人
you are free to walk.
门敞开着
There's the door.
那就把这里收拾干净
Now clean this shit up.
《风骚女子》十分钟内拍摄完毕
"Minx," you have ten minutes to finish.
好的
Okay.
请出去
Please.
谢了 小甜心
Thanks, sugar.
你们知道他的小弟弟
You know his dick is more like Goliath's
比起大卫更像歌利亚的对吧
than David's, right?
-知道 非常大  -我们知道
- Oh, yeah, it's enormous. - We're aware.
-好的  -可以说是巨大了
- Okay, yeah. - It's almost too big.
雷内蒂
Renetti...
很少有人能来我家
Very few men come into my home
像你那样的口气跟我说话
and talk to me like you talk to me,
你打断了决赛
You interrupt the postgame.
-首先  -喔
- First of all, I-- - Whoa! Whoa.
现在你打断我了
Now you're interrupting me.
除此之外
And on top of that...
你指责我的人
you accuse my guys...
你指责我的人偷我的东西
my guys of stealing from me.
关于这事儿
About that, uh--uh...
-嗯  -说实话
- Mm. - The truth is
我不认识你的人
I-I don't know your guys.
但我认识
Well, I do.
他们是我的表兄弟
They're my cousins.
他们是我的妹夫 他们是我的侄子
They're my brother-in-laws. They're my nephews.
他们个个都是混蛋
And every one of them is a freaking piece of shit.
你说对了 雷内蒂 你说对了
You hit the nail right on the head, Renetti-- you did.
有时候需要一个外人
Sometimes it takes someone from the outside to, uh.
才能让人面对残酷的事实
to make one confront an awful truth.
我的整个家族
My whole family--
他们都在掠夺我 我心知肚明
they're all skimming from me, and I know it.
但我困在这个无能的
But I'm trapped in some web
裙带关系里
of--of--of nepotism and incompetence.
坦白说 我很羡慕
And, frankly, I'm jealous of what you
你和这个黑人妞的成就
and this colored broad got.
告诉我 雷内蒂 你的秘诀是什么
So tell me, Renetti, what's your secret here?
如果真有说有什么秘诀 那可能就是
I guess if there's a secret, the secret is, is, um...
雇佣最适合这份工作的人
hire the best people for the job.
黑人 白人 同性恋 异性恋 漂亮的 丑的
Black, white, gay, straight, pretty face, lazy eye...
好人就是好人 就这样
Good people are good people, full stop.
是啊 但是我办公桌上收不到简历
Yeah, well, obviously I don't get resumes
你知道吧
here on my desk, you know?
如果我能组建一个优秀的色情片
Hey, if I can put a winning team together
团队
in porn,
那你肯定也可以给你这个令人印象深刻的
surely you can with all your, you know, legitimate
合法生意组建一个优秀的团队
and impressive businesses
当让我也非常尊重你的生意
that I have so much respect for.
能有什么问题
What is it?
你有经济困难吗 文斯
You having money problems, Vince?
那我问你
So let me ask you--
在财务方面 你最信任谁
who do you trust the most with your finances?
谢谢你帮我洗碗 亲爱的
Thanks for getting the dishes, hon.
没关系
It's fine.
老实说 现在能忙起来的感觉很好
You know, honestly, right now it just feels good to be busy.
-家里有烦心事吗  -工作上
- Trouble at home? - Work.
和那个帅哥有关吗
The handsome fella?
我在和一个不尊重
I am in a partnership with a man
也不重视我的男人共事
who doesn't respect or value me.
没事了 你们不会想听这些的
It's fine. You girls don't want to hear about that.
我们当让想听 西尔维娅的汽车故事我们听了三遍了
Uh, yeah, we do. We've heard Sylvia's car story three times.
明明是两次
That was twice.
我不知道我们今天来这里干什么
I just-- I don't know what we're doing here today.
知道吗 他就带我过来
You know, he brings me here.
我们的目标应该是
Supposedly we want the same thing--
给我们的杂志找广告
to put out our magazine together--
然后他就把我推到一边
and then he just brushes me aside,
他都不知道我做这事有多难
and he has no idea how hard it is to do what I do.
我敢打赌他也很喜欢接受表扬
I bet he's more than happy taking the credit, too.
-你了解道格吗  -我了解男人
- Oh, you know Doug? - I know men.
-嗯嗯  -哈
- Mm-hmm. - Ha!
你们知道吗
You know what?
我看到你们这些女人
I-I see you women,
我也看到你们所拥有的一切
and I see everything that you have, and...
然后我做了不一样的选择
I made a different choice,
但有时候
but some days I just-- I wonder--
我很想知道这个选择到底对不对
I just wonder if that was the right one.
我看了你的杂志 我觉得很可爱
- I saw your magazine. I thought it was cute.
那篇关于避孕的文章 不可接受
That article on birth control, unacceptable.
-你读了吗  -我不需要读
- You read it? - I didn't need to.
我是个虔诚的天主教徒 我知道教会的教义
I'm a good Catholic. I know the Church's teachings.
我尊重也完全理解这种信念 好吗
I respect and I completely understand that faith, okay?
我自己就是个虔诚的圣公会教徒
I'm a good Episcopalian myself.
我是圣公会教徒
Well, I'm Episcopalian.
至少让我跟你说说那篇文章吧
Could I at least tell you about the article?
我想这会让我好受一些
I think it'll make me feel better.
好的 亲爱的
Okay, sweetie.
吃点蛋糕吧
Have some cake.
明天所有的杂志都可以拿去运输了
All the magazines are back
除了《风骚女子》
on the trucks tomorrow, except "Minx."
我努力了 孩子 我无能为力
I tried, kid. There was nothing I could do.
这家伙非常尊重他的妻子
This guy respects his wife like nobody's business.
-说实话  -我以为我要死了
- Well, actually-- - I thought I was a goner.
死翘翘的老雷内蒂
Lights out for old Renetti.
我以为他会杀了我
I thought he was gonna kill me.
他和我对视
He locked eyes with me,
我的心都要炸开了
and, I mean, my heart was exploding.
我知道 但是 我想说
I know, right, but the thing is--
但是别担心好吗
But don't worry about it, okay?
因为我会把《风骚女子》救回来的孩了
Cause I'm gonna get "Minx" back, kid.
我不会放弃《风骚女子》的我会找到办法的
I'm not quitting on "Minx." I will find a way.
我知道你会
I know you will.
我是一个和你干脏活的傻瓜
♪ I'm a fool to do your dirty work... ♪
太棒了
These are amazing.
这些镜头让他从神坛上下来
Taking him off the pedestal in a series of shots
消除了理想化的美所特有的
just eliminates the-- the oppression
压迫
endemic to idealized beauty.
我们把他拍出了可以看的样子
We've made it okay to look.
这正是我们想要的
That's exactly what we were going for.
做的很棒 伙计们
Really great job, guys.
噢 是的
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
昨天怎么样了
Hey, how'd it go yesterday?
平淡无奇 你呢
Uneventful. You?
我也差不多
About the same.
我在工作室时间和设备上
I did make some policy changes
做了一些政策上的改变
on studio time and equipment.
-你批准吗  -批准
- You want to approve? - Approved.
我雇你是个明智的选择
Hey, I made a good choice when I hired you.
从那以后 我每天都心存感激
And I'm thankful for that every day since.
很抱歉我不能每天给你表达我的感激
I'm, um-- I'm sorry if I don't tell you that enough.
道格 你的电话
Phone call, Doug.
-我该接电话了  -嗯嗯
- I should take that. - Mm-hmm.
你该
You should.
我不想帮你干脏活
♪ I don't wanna do your dirty work ♪
谢谢
Thank you.
不再
♪ No more ♪
《风骚女子》回来了 避孕文章也一起回归
"Minx" is back on the trucks, birth control article and all.
不是吧
You don't say.
我想我给文斯留下的印象
I guess I made a bigger impression
比我想象的要深刻
on Vince than I thought.
幸运的是 我们对你的文章
Luckily, we didn't get too far
没有谈的太深入
on that hatchet job on your article.
现在回想起来
Well, in retrospect,
你的想法真有见地
that was a very resourceful idea that you had.
谢谢你 你能这么说真是太好了
Thank you. That's, um, big of you to say.
你是老板
You're the boss.
有一个恋爱中的女理发师
♪ There was an in-love lady barber ♪
她想要她得不到的东西
♪ Who wanted what she could not have ♪
她爬得太高了
♪ She climbed up the mountains too high ♪
她一次又一次地摔倒
♪ She fell over and over again ♪
她想捕捉阳光
♪ She wanted to capture the sunshine ♪
去触摸每一滴崭新的雨珠
♪ To touch each brand-new drop of rain ♪
穿越彩虹
♪ To travel the length of a rainbow ♪
再也不要回来了
♪ And never come back again ♪
她想躺在草甸里
♪ She wanted to lie in straw meadows ♪
处处感受资本之爱
♪ To feel capital love everywhere ♪
但在她内心深处
♪ Yet way, way down deep, deep inside her ♪
她不知道自己是否真的在乎
♪ She wondered if she really cared ♪
有一个恋爱中的女理发师
♪ There was an in-love lady barber ♪
她想要她得不到的东西
♪ Who wanted what she could not have ♪
她爬得太高了
♪ She climbed up the mountains too high ♪